http://www.ams.usda.gov/about-ams/privacy

Privacy Statement | Agricultural Marketing Service
Skip to main content
An official website of the United States government
Here's how you know
The .gov means it’s official.
Federal government websites always use a .gov or .mil domain. Before sharing sensitive information online, make sure you’re on a .gov or .mil site by inspecting your browser’s address (or “location”) bar.
This site is also protected by an SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) certificate that’s been signed by the U.S. government. The https:// means all transmitted data is encrypted
— in other words, any information or browsing history that you provide is transmitted securely.
Menu
Agricultural Marketing Service
U.S. Department of Agriculture
Home
Market News
Market News
Cotton and Tobacco
Dairy
Cotton and Tobacco
Country of Origin Labeling (COOL)
Dairy Forward Contracting
Federal Seed Act
Food Quality Protection Act
Food Security Act
Hemp
Mandatory Market Reporting
Marketing Orders & Agreements
Organic Regulations
Packers and Stockyards Act
Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA)
Pesticide Record Keeping
Plant Variety Protection Act
Proposed Rules
Research & Promotion Programs
Section 8e & Imports
Shell Egg Surveillance
US Grain Standards Act
Rulemaking
Product Specifications & Requirements
Web-Based Supply Chain Management (WBSCM)
Small Business Opportunities
Contact Commodity Procurement
Annual Industry Meeting
Search
Search
About AMS
News & Announcements
Contact Us
USDA Farmers Market
Information presented on the AMS web site is considered public information and may be distributed or copied. Use of appropriate byline/photo/image credits is requested.
AMS is committed to maintaining a web site that protects the individual’s right to privacy. We do not require personal information from our visitors, nor do we collect any personally identifying information (name, email address, Social Security number, or other unique identifier) unless you knowingly provide it. Likewise, we do not give, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party.
Data Collection for Statistics
This website uses Google Analytics Premium. Please refer to the following policies on Google’s website for more information:
Google’s main privacy policy
Cookies & Google Analytics on Websites
Opt out of Google Analytics Cookies
To aid in web site management, certain information is collected for statistical purposes. AMS uses Google Analytics to create summary statistics, which are used to make our website more useful and accessible to visitors.
We collect the following information about your visit:
The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, "princeton.edu" if you are connecting from Princeton University’s domain, or "aol.com" if you are connecting from an America Online account);
The web site from which you linked directly to our web site, if you have used another web site to reach the AMS web site;
The operating system and web browser you use to view pages;
The date and time you access our web site;
The country from which you are connecting; and
The pages viewed during your visit.
Information Collected from E-mails and Forms
You may decide to send us personally identifying information through e-mail messages or through on-line forms. Electronic communication allows us to collect information that will improve our web site for you, and we encourage it. You should know that we use information provided in e-mails and forms only for the purposes provided, and the information will be destroyed after its purpose has been fulfilled, in accordance with the National Archives and Records Administration General Schedule 20.
Security Checks
For web site security purposes, and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, AMS employs software programs to monitor network traffic, identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on this web site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
Surveys
This web site may occasionally use voluntary on-line user surveys designed to provide information for the government to improve this web site. When using these surveys, this web site may also use technology known as “persistent cookies” to distinguish users that have previously completed the survey from those that have not. No personally identifying information is collected from the use of this technology, and its purpose is to present the survey invitations only to users that have not completed the survey. If you wish to opt-out from the use of the persistent cookie, you may do so by following the instructions at the following link: http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml. If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please forward them to AMSWebmaster@usda.gov.
Return to top
Home
Market News
Rules & Regulations
Grades & Standards
Services
Resources
Commodity Procurement
